var bank = [
    {
        "answer": "the range of operation, authority, control, concern, etc.",
        "question": "purview",
        "info": "\"Admitting refugees lies solely in the purview of the federal government, and states cannot legally refuse to accept immigrants.\"",
        "id": 0
    },
    {
        "answer": "immature or inexperienced",
        "question": "callow",
        "info": "\"Those days have changed, and with our lively wit, sparkling conversation and wealth of life experience, we can add as much, if not more, to the gaiety than any callow, tongue-tied youth.\"",
        "id": 1
    },
    {
        "answer": "a slight infusion, as of some element or quality",
        "question": "tincture",
        "info": "\"A tincture of education had softened his rude manners.\"",
        "id": 2
    },
    {
        "answer": "using many fancy words; highly rhetorical",
        "question": "purple",
        "info": "\"Her writing was full of purple prose.\"",
        "id": 3
    },
    {
        "answer": "authorized or generally accepted theory, doctrine, or practice",
        "question": "orthodoxy",
        "info": "\"This history, along with the facts that sexual assault is notoriously underreported and that the crime suffers no more false reports than other crimes\u2014and the related idea that only those actually assaulted would take on the burden of coming forward\u2014leads many advocates today to the \u201calways believe\u201d orthodoxy.\"",
        "id": 4
    },
    {
        "answer": "keen insight",
        "question": "acumen",
        "info": "\"Thorndike also points out that most CEOs get their jobs not through exhibiting financial acumen, but for excellence in some other area, like production, marketing or sales.\"",
        "id": 5
    },
    {
        "answer": "cheerful readiness, promptness, or willingness",
        "question": "alacrity",
        "info": "\"In New York City, mastering the art of riding the subway requires a bit of practice, alacrity, and luck.\"",
        "id": 6
    },
    {
        "answer": "for a still stronger reason",
        "question": "a fortiori",
        "info": "\"If Britain cannot afford a space programme, then, a fortiori, neither can India.\"",
        "id": 7
    },
    {
        "answer": "deceptive; misleading",
        "question": "fallacious",
        "info": "\"Other times it\u2019s not fair: The old \u201cwine is bullshit\u201d trope paints an entire drink with a broad, obviously fallacious brush, and encourages people to just give up on something they may enjoy instead of learning about it.\"",
        "id": 8
    },
    {
        "answer": "to put forward or offer for consideration, acceptance, or adoption; set forth; propose",
        "question": "propound",
        "info": "\"Is it humble to publicly propound the virtues of humility?\"",
        "id": 9
    },
    {
        "answer": "an intervening episode, period, space, etc.",
        "question": "interlude",
        "info": "\"After rare seasonal interlude, a return to Easter warmth\"",
        "id": 10
    },
    {
        "answer": "a person who does not know much; an ignorant or stupid person",
        "question": "ignoramus",
        "id": 11
    },
    {
        "answer": "a slight suggestion or indication; hint; intimation",
        "question": "inkling",
        "id": 12
    },
    {
        "answer": "a slight suggestion or indication; hint; intimation",
        "question": "inkling",
        "id": 13
    },
    {
        "answer": "an accidental advantage; stroke of good luck",
        "question": "fluke",
        "id": 14
    },
    {
        "answer": "intellectually or morally ignorant; unenlightened",
        "question": "benighted",
        "id": 15
    },
    {
        "answer": "unusual in a playful or amusing way; not serious",
        "question": "whimsical",
        "id": 16
    },
    {
        "answer": "very large and impressive, like a palace",
        "question": "palatial",
        "id": 17
    },
    {
        "answer": "perform better than usual in response to a special situation or event",
        "question": "rise to the occasion",
        "id": 18
    },
    {
        "answer": "serving or acting as an instrument or means; useful; helpful",
        "question": "instrumental",
        "id": 19
    },
    {
        "answer": "as; as being",
        "question": "qua",
        "info": "\"The work of art qua art can be judged by aesthetic criteria only.\"",
        "id": 20
    },
    {
        "answer": "an area of muddy or boggy ground; a complicated or confused situation",
        "question": "morass",
        "id": 21
    },
    {
        "answer": "the process or result of fusing items into one entity; fusion",
        "question": "conflation",
        "info": "\"The conflation of anti-Semitism and anti-Israel sentiments is nothing new.\"",
        "id": 22
    },
    {
        "answer": "critical explanation or interpretation of a text or portion of a text, especially of the Bible",
        "question": "exegesis",
        "id": 23
    },
    {
        "answer": "easily persuaded to believe something; credulous",
        "question": "gullible",
        "id": 24
    },
    {
        "answer": "a strange or peculiar person or thing",
        "question": "oddity",
        "id": 25
    },
    {
        "answer": "having an appearance of truth or reason; seemingly worthy of approval or acceptance",
        "question": "plausible",
        "id": 26
    },
    {
        "answer": "the art of investigating or discussing the truth of opinions",
        "question": "dialectics",
        "id": 27
    },
    {
        "answer": "a stupid or foolish person",
        "question": "numbskull",
        "id": 28
    },
    {
        "answer": "until now or until the point in time under discussion",
        "question": "hitherto",
        "id": 29
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a disease or poison) extremely severe or harmful in its effects; bitterly hostile",
        "question": "virulent",
        "info": "\"That holds especially true for women, who get more virulent and violent responses than men for anything they do in the public sphere.\"",
        "id": 30
    },
    {
        "answer": "a tedious recital or repetitive series",
        "question": "litany",
        "info": "\"A litany of lines pay homage to the original trilogy, as do several familiar minor characters and plot points.\"",
        "id": 31
    },
    {
        "answer": "a state of perplexity or uncertainty over what to do in a difficult situation",
        "question": "quandary",
        "info": "\"I logged onto a new app called Koko and posted about my quandary.\"",
        "id": 32
    },
    {
        "answer": "a phrase indicating that the speaker is introducing parallel or closely contrasting information",
        "question": "by the same token",
        "info": "\"University athletes are happy to be in the news, but by the same token, they must not be distracted from their studies.\"",
        "id": 33
    },
    {
        "answer": "in an express manner; explicitly",
        "question": "expressly",
        "id": 34
    },
    {
        "answer": "to such an extent (usually followed by as)",
        "question": "insofar",
        "info": "\"I will do the work insofar as I am able.\"",
        "id": 35
    },
    {
        "answer": "a small and particularly interesting item of gossip or information",
        "question": "titbit",
        "info": "\"They were hoping for titbit about the family\"",
        "id": 36
    },
    {
        "answer": "genuine and legitimate",
        "question": "kosher",
        "id": 37
    },
    {
        "answer": "a source of help in a difficult situation",
        "question": "recourse",
        "id": 38
    },
    {
        "answer": "comfort or consolation in a time of great distress or sadness",
        "question": "solace",
        "id": 39
    },
    {
        "answer": "leave (property) to a person or other beneficiary by a will",
        "question": "bequeath",
        "id": 40
    },
    {
        "answer": "imperturbable self-possession, poise, or assurance",
        "question": "aplomb",
        "id": 41
    },
    {
        "answer": "unintentionally reveal; be evidence of",
        "question": "betray",
        "info": "\"She drew a deep breath that betray her indignation\"",
        "id": 42
    },
    {
        "answer": "in any case; anyway",
        "question": "at any rate",
        "id": 43
    },
    {
        "answer": "having or showing a definite tendency, bias, or purpose",
        "question": "tendentious",
        "id": 44
    },
    {
        "answer": "incapable of being solved or explained",
        "question": "insoluble",
        "id": 45
    },
    {
        "answer": "mystical, supernatural, or magical powers, practices, or phenomena",
        "question": "occult",
        "info": "\"Age and experience had sharpened Clara\u2019s ability to divine the occult and to move objects from afar.\"",
        "id": 46
    },
    {
        "answer": "rare, exotic, or obscure",
        "question": "recherch\u00e9",
        "info": "\"A few linguistic terms are perhaps a bit recherch\u00e9 for the average readership\"",
        "id": 47
    },
    {
        "answer": "no matter what might happen",
        "question": "come what may",
        "id": 48
    },
    {
        "answer": "having a limited or narrow outlook or scope",
        "question": "parochial",
        "info": "\"These shortsighted parochial decisions at the expense of the national interest are precisely the kind that the public suspects the government routinely makes.\"",
        "id": 49
    },
    {
        "answer": "make a deep inarticulate sound conveying pain, despair, pleasure, etc.",
        "question": "groan",
        "id": 50
    },
    {
        "answer": "make twisting, squirming movements or contortions of the body",
        "question": "writhe",
        "id": 51
    },
    {
        "answer": "forbidden or prohibited",
        "question": "verboten",
        "info": "\"Ultimately, to discuss the relationship between guns, white men, masculinity and mass violence in America is verboten.\"",
        "id": 52
    },
    {
        "answer": "an event or period marking a turning point in a situation",
        "question": "watershed",
        "info": "\"The Chicago meeting was the watershed moment in the atomic bomb project.\"",
        "id": 53
    },
    {
        "answer": "things wanted or needed",
        "question": "desiderata",
        "id": 54
    },
    {
        "answer": "evade the truth of a point or question by raising irrelevant objections; argue over petty things",
        "question": "quibble",
        "info": "\"People will quibble with the implementation, but on the whole it feels thoughtfully designed.\"",
        "id": 55
    },
    {
        "answer": "out of regard or respect for (a person or the person's position or wishes)",
        "question": "in deference to",
        "id": 56
    },
    {
        "answer": "rule of personal conduct",
        "question": "precept",
        "id": 57
    },
    {
        "answer": "a doctrine that is taught",
        "question": "precept",
        "info": "\"Reconciling the religious precept of observant Muslims with the secular norms in the European workplace has long been a sensitive subject.\"",
        "id": 58
    },
    {
        "answer": "take as a given; assume as a postulate or axiom",
        "question": "posit",
        "info": "\"He posit three basic laws of nature\"",
        "id": 59
    },
    {
        "answer": "the range of operation, authority, control, concern, etc.",
        "question": "purview",
        "id": 60
    },
    {
        "answer": "to acknowledge as true, just, or proper; admit",
        "question": "concede",
        "id": 61
    },
    {
        "answer": "characterized by or given to extreme optimism, especially in the face of unrelieved hardship or adversity",
        "question": "Panglossian",
        "info": "\"The Panglossian view of natural selection is an appealing idea to us as human beings, you argue, because brains have foresight.\"",
        "id": 62
    },
    {
        "answer": "use parts of something to repair something else",
        "question": "cannibalize",
        "info": "\"Cook has already said he\u2019s unafraid of cannibalize the Mac business, and he sees the iPad as a bigger threat to Windows PCs anyway.\"",
        "id": 63
    },
    {
        "answer": "any disease-producing agent (especially a virus or bacterium or other microorganism)",
        "question": "pathogen",
        "info": "\"In biology, a pathogen in the oldest and broadest sense is anything that can produce disease, a term which came into use in the 1880s.\"",
        "id": 64
    },
    {
        "answer": "be relevant to",
        "question": "pertain",
        "info": "\"In October, The Times filed a public records request seeking documentation pertain to the investigation.\"",
        "id": 65
    },
    {
        "answer": "surround and restrict the space or movement of someone or something",
        "question": "hem",
        "id": 66
    },
    {
        "answer": "actions that cause great irritation (or even anger)",
        "question": "exasperation",
        "info": "\"Smugness, exasperation and partisanship are certainly apparent but kept generally in low gear \u2014 except when Hayden writes about Congress or the media.\"",
        "id": 67
    },
    {
        "answer": "approach or extend the limits of what is possible",
        "question": "push the envelope (or the edge of the envelope)",
        "id": 68
    },
    {
        "answer": "a person who takes part in a dialogue or conversation",
        "question": "interlocutor",
        "id": 69
    },
    {
        "answer": "a violent or sudden change or disruption to something",
        "question": "upheaval",
        "id": 71
    },
    {
        "answer": "a large amount of writing",
        "question": "ream",
        "id": 72
    },
    {
        "answer": "behaviour in keeping with good taste and propriety",
        "question": "decorum",
        "id": 74
    },
    {
        "answer": "a difficult or disagreeable obligation, task, burden, etc.",
        "question": "onus",
        "id": 75
    },
    {
        "answer": "open to view or knowledge; not concealed or secret",
        "question": "overt",
        "id": 76
    },
    {
        "answer": "a harmful action",
        "question": "disservice",
        "id": 77
    },
    {
        "answer": "outwardly appearing as such",
        "question": "ostensible",
        "id": 78
    },
    {
        "answer": "(especially with reference to creative work) the most important or remarkable feature",
        "question": "pi\u00e8ce de r\u00e9sistance",
        "id": 79
    },
    {
        "answer": "a ghost or spirit supposed to manifest its presence by noises, knockings, etc.",
        "question": "poltergeist",
        "id": 80
    },
    {
        "answer": "suitable for or suggestive of an idyll; charmingly simple or rustic",
        "question": "idyllic",
        "id": 81
    },
    {
        "answer": "at the first glimpse or impression",
        "question": "at first blush",
        "id": 82
    },
    {
        "answer": "smallness of quantity",
        "question": "paucity",
        "id": 83
    },
    {
        "answer": "lasting for a very short time",
        "question": "ephemeral",
        "id": 84
    },
    {
        "answer": "an extremely confused, complicated, or embarrassing situation",
        "question": "imbroglio",
        "id": 85
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a sound) pleasingly smooth and musical to hear",
        "question": "mellifluous",
        "id": 86
    },
    {
        "answer": "flagrantly wicked or impious",
        "question": "nefarious",
        "id": 87
    },
    {
        "answer": "nearness of blood",
        "question": "propinquity",
        "id": 88
    },
    {
        "answer": "overabundance; excess",
        "question": "plethora",
        "info": "\"a plethora of advice and a paucity of assistance\"",
        "id": 89
    },
    {
        "answer": "showing a deliberate and obstinate desire to behave in a way that is unreasonable or unacceptable",
        "question": "perverse",
        "id": 90
    },
    {
        "answer": "be inspired with an intense but short-lived passion or admiration for",
        "question": "infatuate",
        "id": 91
    },
    {
        "answer": "to make a transition from one thing to another smoothly and without interruption",
        "question": "segue",
        "id": 92
    },
    {
        "answer": "to agree or concur",
        "question": "assent",
        "id": 93
    },
    {
        "answer": "fit or suitable for drinking",
        "question": "potable",
        "id": 94
    },
    {
        "answer": "different in kind; unlike; incongruous",
        "question": "heterogeneous",
        "id": 95
    },
    {
        "answer": "to hold in the mind",
        "question": "entertain",
        "id": 96
    },
    {
        "answer": "courteous, gracious, and having a sophisticated charm",
        "question": "debonair",
        "id": 97
    },
    {
        "answer": "to credit or assign, as to a cause or source; attribute",
        "question": "ascribe",
        "id": 98
    },
    {
        "answer": "equivalent, as in value, force, effect, or signification",
        "question": "tantamount",
        "id": 99
    },
    {
        "answer": "providing or serving for the time being only; existing only until permanently or properly replaced; temporary",
        "question": "provisional",
        "id": 100
    },
    {
        "answer": "something uttered; a word or words uttered",
        "question": "utterance",
        "id": 101
    },
    {
        "answer": "to show activity, movement, or life; grow or spread gradually",
        "question": "percolate",
        "id": 102
    },
    {
        "answer": "not one or the other; not something fitting any category under discussion",
        "question": "neither fish nor fowl",
        "info": "\"They felt he was neither fish nor fowl - not qualified to lead the department, yet not appropriate to work as a staff member either.\"",
        "id": 103
    },
    {
        "answer": "distress or suffering resulting from oppression or persecution",
        "question": "tribulation",
        "id": 104
    },
    {
        "answer": "a large, challenging task",
        "question": "tough row to hoe",
        "id": 105
    },
    {
        "answer": "a series of words said as a magic spell or charm",
        "question": "incantation",
        "id": 106
    },
    {
        "answer": "the worship of idols",
        "question": "idolatry",
        "id": 107
    },
    {
        "answer": "exclude from a society or group",
        "question": "ostracize",
        "id": 108
    },
    {
        "answer": "extremely idealistic; unrealistic and impractical",
        "question": "quixotic",
        "id": 109
    },
    {
        "answer": "a broad strip or area of something",
        "question": "swathe",
        "id": 110
    },
    {
        "answer": "a custom, principle, or belief distinguishing a particular class or group of people, especially a long-standing one regarded as outmoded or no longer important",
        "question": "shibboleth",
        "id": 111
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of speech or writing) continuing at tedious length",
        "question": "long-winded",
        "id": 112
    },
    {
        "answer": "not likely to cause offence or disagreement and somewhat dull",
        "question": "anodyne",
        "id": 113
    },
    {
        "answer": "clearly expressed and easily understood; lucid",
        "question": "perspicuous",
        "id": 114
    },
    {
        "answer": "a strong feeling that something is about to happen, especially something unpleasant",
        "question": "premonition",
        "id": 115
    },
    {
        "answer": "pertaining to color or colors",
        "question": "chromatic",
        "id": 116
    },
    {
        "answer": "to plan with ingenuity; devise; invent",
        "question": "contrive",
        "id": 117
    },
    {
        "answer": "truthful; veracious",
        "question": "veridical",
        "id": 118
    },
    {
        "answer": "unsure; uncertain; not definite or positive; hesitant",
        "question": "tentative",
        "id": 119
    },
    {
        "answer": "mutually destructive",
        "question": "internecine",
        "id": 120
    },
    {
        "answer": "to make a transition from one thing to another smoothly and without interruption",
        "question": "segue",
        "id": 121
    },
    {
        "answer": "unable to be resisted or avoided; inescapable",
        "question": "ineluctable",
        "id": 122
    },
    {
        "answer": "unable to be resisted or avoided; inescapable",
        "question": "ineluctable",
        "info": "\"Absolute solitude is on this showing the ineluctable destiny of the soul. Only our bodies can meet.\"",
        "id": 123
    },
    {
        "answer": "having or showing an ability to accurately assess situations or people and turn this to one's advantage",
        "question": "astute",
        "id": 124
    },
    {
        "answer": "done without good reason; uncalled for",
        "question": "gratuitous",
        "id": 125
    },
    {
        "answer": "giving off radiation",
        "question": "radiative",
        "id": 126
    },
    {
        "answer": "a principle or set of principles laid down by an authority as incontrovertibly true",
        "question": "dogma",
        "id": 127
    },
    {
        "answer": "a collection or gathering of things or people",
        "question": "assemblage",
        "id": 128
    },
    {
        "answer": "be entailed by or consequent on the existence or establishment of another",
        "question": "supervene",
        "info": "\"Machine translation necessarily supervene on previous human effort; otherwise there wouldn\u2019t be the parallel corpora that the machines need to do their work.\"",
        "id": 129
    },
    {
        "answer": "adaptable, tractable",
        "question": "malleable",
        "id": 130
    },
    {
        "answer": "aggravate",
        "question": "exacerbate",
        "id": 131
    },
    {
        "answer": "a riddle; a puzzle",
        "question": "conundrum",
        "id": 132
    },
    {
        "answer": "to beg urgently or piteously, as for aid or mercy;beseech ;entreat",
        "question": "implore",
        "id": 133
    },
    {
        "answer": "to satisfy fully; to fill to excess",
        "question": "sate",
        "info": "synonym: glut",
        "id": 134
    },
    {
        "answer": "a feeling of utter weariness and discontent resulting from satiety or lack of interest; boredom",
        "question": "ennui",
        "info": "\"The endless lecture produced an un beatable ennui.\"",
        "id": 135
    },
    {
        "answer": "the state of being satiated; surfeit",
        "question": "satiety",
        "id": 136
    },
    {
        "answer": "to supply with anything to excess",
        "question": "surfeit",
        "id": 137
    },
    {
        "answer": "to supply with anything to excess, so as to disgust or weary; surfeit",
        "question": "satiate",
        "id": 138
    },
    {
        "answer": "spotlessly clean",
        "question": "immaculate",
        "id": 139
    },
    {
        "answer": "in exactly the same word; word for word",
        "question": "verbatim",
        "id": 140
    },
    {
        "answer": "in fact",
        "question": "de facto",
        "id": 141
    },
    {
        "answer": "close relation; connection, especially harmonious or sympathetic relation",
        "question": "rapport",
        "id": 142
    },
    {
        "answer": "to join or fit together compactly or harmoniously",
        "question": "dovetail",
        "id": 143
    },
    {
        "answer": "as an aside",
        "question": "parenthetically",
        "id": 144
    },
    {
        "answer": "the property of having a definite location at any given time",
        "question": "ubiety",
        "id": 145
    },
    {
        "answer": "to make known; tell; disclose",
        "question": "impart",
        "info": "\"to impart knowledge\"",
        "id": 146
    },
    {
        "answer": "to cause someone to feel enthusiasm or be enthusiastic",
        "question": "enthuse",
        "id": 147
    },
    {
        "answer": "steer (a boat or ship)",
        "question": "helm",
        "info": "\"With Sundar at the helm, where does Google fit in the Alphabet?\"",
        "id": 148
    },
    {
        "answer": "filled with vigor",
        "question": "animated",
        "id": 149
    },
    {
        "answer": "privately owned articles consisting chiefly of clothing, toilet items, etc., for intimate use by an individual",
        "question": "personal effects",
        "id": 150
    },
    {
        "answer": "privately owned articles consisting chiefly of furniture, appliance, etc., for keeping house",
        "question": "household effects",
        "id": 151
    },
    {
        "answer": "instill or teach (an idea, attitude, or habit) by persistent instruction",
        "question": "inculcate",
        "id": 152
    },
    {
        "answer": "in every practical sense",
        "question": "for all intents and purposes",
        "id": 153
    },
    {
        "answer": "taken or considered as a whole",
        "question": "in the aggregate",
        "info": "\"In the aggregate, our losses have been relatively small.\"",
        "id": 154
    },
    {
        "answer": "to make speechless with amazement; astonish",
        "question": "dumbfound",
        "id": 155
    },
    {
        "answer": "not to be persuaded, moved, or affected by prayers or entreaties",
        "question": "inexorable",
        "id": 156
    },
    {
        "answer": "understood without being openly expressed; implied",
        "question": "tacit",
        "info": "\"a tacit approval by smiling\"",
        "id": 157
    },
    {
        "answer": "to assent tacitly; submit or comply silently or without protest",
        "question": "acquiesce",
        "info": "\"to acquiesce halfheartedly in a business plan\"",
        "id": 158
    },
    {
        "answer": "a situation from which extrication is very difficult",
        "question": "quagmire",
        "id": 159
    },
    {
        "answer": "an unpleasantly difficult, perplexing, or dangerous situation",
        "question": "predicament",
        "id": 160
    },
    {
        "answer": "dependent on circumstances beyond one's control; uncertain; unstable; insecure",
        "question": "precarious",
        "id": 161
    },
    {
        "answer": "alongside each other",
        "question": "in tandem",
        "info": "\"a tight fiscal policy working in tandem with a tight foreign exchange policy\"",
        "id": 162
    },
    {
        "answer": " to occur or turn out as suspected or intended",
        "question": "come to fruition",
        "info": "\"When will all of these good things come to fruition?\"",
        "id": 163
    },
    {
        "answer": "to follow the example of",
        "question": "borrow a page from",
        "id": 164
    },
    {
        "answer": "a person who is an inspiration to others",
        "question": "luminary",
        "id": 165
    },
    {
        "answer": "a saying that sets forth a general truth and that has gained credit through long use",
        "question": "adage",
        "id": 166
    },
    {
        "answer": "praiseworthy",
        "question": "laudable",
        "id": 167
    },
    {
        "answer": "appease the anger or anxiety of (someone)",
        "question": "mollify",
        "id": 168
    },
    {
        "answer": "(something unpleasant) continuing without pause or interruption",
        "question": "incessant",
        "id": 169
    },
    {
        "answer": "incapable of being fully understood",
        "question": "unfathomable",
        "id": 170
    },
    {
        "answer": "to envy or resent the pleasure or good fortune of (someone)",
        "question": "begrudge",
        "info": "\"She begrudge her friend the award.\"",
        "id": 171
    },
    {
        "answer": "for the special purpose or end presently under consideration",
        "question": "ad hoc",
        "info": "\"a committee formed ad hoc to deal with the issue\"",
        "id": 172
    },
    {
        "answer": "appealing to one's prejudices, emotions, or special interests rather than to one's intellect or reason",
        "question": "ad hominem",
        "info": "\"ad hominem attack\"",
        "id": 173
    },
    {
        "answer": "the original pattern or model from which all things of the same kind are copied or on which they are based; a model or first form; prototype",
        "question": "archetype",
        "info": "\"Women isn\u2019t advanced gender theory or radical feminism, but a series of videos about recognizing common narrative themes and archetypes.\"",
        "id": 174
    },
    {
        "answer": "practicing great self-denial; severely simple",
        "question": "austere",
        "info": "\"A swaybacked roof side by side with an austere perpendicular brick building: so beautiful.\"",
        "id": 175
    },
    {
        "answer": "repeated too often; overfamiliar through overuse",
        "question": "banal",
        "info": "\"tactics range from crude violence to banal efficiency.\"",
        "id": 176
    },
    {
        "answer": "inclined or eager to fight; aggressively hostile",
        "question": "bellicose",
        "id": 177
    },
    {
        "answer": "saying offensive things about God or religion",
        "question": "blasphemy",
        "info": "\"Salman Rushdie, novelist accused of blasphemy against Islam for his book \u201cThe Satanic Verses\u201d\"",
        "id": 178
    },
    {
        "answer": "a deliberately misleading fabrication",
        "question": "canard",
        "info": "\"Our beatitudinal myth of posterity\u2014blessed are the unknown geniuses, for they shall be super-famous after they die\u2014is a canard.\"",
        "id": 179
    },
    {
        "answer": "(music) a gradual increase in loudness",
        "question": "crescendo",
        "info": "\"Throughout the night, the call periodically rose again, reaching a crescendo as the final minutes ticked down.\"",
        "id": 180
    },
    {
        "answer": "a heavy rain; an overwhelming number or amount",
        "question": "deluge",
        "info": "\"These same groups must also work to stop the deluge of bots that attempt to hide behind the conceit that they are real humans.\"",
        "id": 181
    },
    {
        "answer": "a political leader who seeks support by appealing to popular passions and prejudices",
        "question": "demagogue",
        "info": "\"Trump is the least electable Republican presidential candidate in a generation, a sinister demagogue who would almost certainly lose to Hillary Clinton in November.\"",
        "id": 182
    },
    {
        "answer": "thunderous verbal attack",
        "question": "diatribe",
        "info": "\"For some, Trump\u2019s diatribes against undocumented immigrants, Mexicans and Muslims evoke unpleasant flashbacks of dictators.\"",
        "id": 183
    },
    {
        "answer": "selecting what seems best of various styles or ideas",
        "question": "eclectic",
        "info": "\"He\u2019d spent most of his childhood inside, reading the eclectic books in his mother\u2019s library.\"",
        "id": 184
    },
    {
        "answer": "make clear and (more) comprehensible",
        "question": "elucidate",
        "info": "\"Can you please elucidate why the NYT is conducting any part of an interview with a Presidential candidate off the record?\"",
        "id": 185
    },
    {
        "answer": "a state of deep-seated ill-will",
        "question": "enmity",
        "info": "\"The solution, though, is not to provoke international enmity and trade conflict by adopting a hostile attitude toward would-be trading partners.\"",
        "id": 186
    },
    {
        "answer": "a standard or typical example; a brief abstract (as of an article or book)",
        "question": "epitome",
        "info": "\"Odd Future was the epitome of this new statelessness: They were neither engineered by a label nor hometown heroes, but something wildly different.\"",
        "id": 187
    },
    {
        "answer": "confined to and understandable by only an enlightened inner circle",
        "question": "esoteric",
        "info": "\"Probably as a young artist I wouldn\u2019t have said that, because I was too interested in the esoteric edge.\"",
        "id": 188
    },
    {
        "answer": "the apparent surface of the imaginary sphere on which celestial bodies appear to be projected; the curve of the sky",
        "question": "firmament",
        "info": "\"Sanders\u2019 criticisms of Clinton have often been couched with some respect for her family\u2019s place in the Democratic firmament.\"",
        "id": 189
    },
    {
        "answer": "of goods or commodities; freely exchangeable for or replaceable by another of like nature or kind in the satisfaction of an obligation",
        "question": "fungible",
        "id": 190
    },
    {
        "answer": "a temporary leave of absence from (military duty)",
        "question": "furlough",
        "info": "\"Some workers said they were preparing for the possibility they may remain on furloughs until retirement.\"",
        "id": 191
    },
    {
        "answer": "relevant and appropriate",
        "question": "germane",
        "id": 192
    },
    {
        "answer": "instinctively or temperamentally seeking and enjoying the company of others; (of animals) tending to form a group with others of the same species",
        "question": "gregarious",
        "info": "\"All told they indicate a gregarious man, busy and disciplined, making excellent use of his gifts.\"",
        "id": 193
    },
    {
        "answer": "an offensive or disparaging expression that is substituted for an inoffensive one",
        "question": "dysphemism",
        "id": 194
    },
    {
        "answer": "beautiful handwriting",
        "question": "penmanship",
        "id": 195
    },
    {
        "answer": "shallow; lacking seriousness",
        "question": "flippant",
        "id": 196
    },
    {
        "answer": "to use or take advantage of existing thing as a basis or support",
        "question": "piggyback",
        "id": 197
    },
    {
        "answer": "a representation of a person that is exaggerated for comic effect",
        "question": "caricature",
        "id": 198
    },
    {
        "answer": "a terse saying embodying a general truth, or astute observation",
        "question": "aphorism",
        "id": 199
    },
    {
        "answer": "repeat something not fully understood",
        "question": "regurgitate",
        "id": 200
    },
    {
        "answer": "to entertain lavishly",
        "question": "regale",
        "id": 201
    },
    {
        "answer": "admitted belonging to a group",
        "question": "card-carrying",
        "id": 202
    },
    {
        "answer": "prevalent, common, frequent",
        "question": "rife",
        "info": "\"Nature is rife with complexities.\"",
        "id": 203
    },
    {
        "answer": "a cliff with a vertical overhanging face; a situation of great peril",
        "question": "precipice",
        "info": "\"on the precipice of defeat\"",
        "id": 204
    },
    {
        "answer": "the final issue, the conclusion, the result",
        "question": "upshot",
        "info": "\"In the 16th century, the last arrow launched in an archery competition was called the upshot.\"",
        "id": 205
    },
    {
        "answer": "incapable of being investigated",
        "question": "inscrutable",
        "id": 206
    },
    {
        "answer": "the collective fans of something",
        "question": "fandom",
        "info": "\"The idea that Batman doesn't kill people is usually seen as sacrosanct within the fandom.\"",
        "id": 207
    },
    {
        "answer": "inviolable, regarded as too important or valuable to be interfered",
        "question": "sacrosanct",
        "info": "\"The idea that Batman doesn't kill people is usually seen as sacrosanct within the fandom.\"",
        "id": 208
    },
    {
        "answer": "understand something difficult or enigmatic after much thought",
        "question": "fathom",
        "id": 209
    },
    {
        "answer": "having or characterized by many transient sexual relationship",
        "question": "promiscuous",
        "id": 210
    },
    {
        "answer": "abnormally sensitive, obsessive, or anxious",
        "question": "neurotic",
        "id": 211
    },
    {
        "answer": "being or relating to or bearing the name of an eponym",
        "question": "eponymous",
        "info": "\"He drew a distinction, however, in his criticism of Trump\u2019s business record -- including the mogul\u2019s now-defunct eponymous university.\"",
        "id": 212
    },
    {
        "answer": "something that precedes and indicates the approach of something or someone",
        "question": "harbinger",
        "info": "\"It was audacious and ugly \u2013 a harbinger of things to come in this nasty election cycle.\"",
        "id": 213
    },
    {
        "answer": "the dominance or leadership of one social group or nation over others",
        "question": "hegemony",
        "info": "\"Regarding the overseas potentates that threaten your hegemony, you should refrain from the temptation of negotiating with them.\"",
        "id": 214
    },
    {
        "answer": "overbearing pride or presumption",
        "question": "hubris",
        "info": "\"Nobel Prize winners, academics and economists are interviewed, and while they mention numerous reasons for these meltdowns, hubris is often cited as the chief culprit.\"",
        "id": 215
    },
    {
        "answer": "exemption from punishment or loss",
        "question": "impunity",
        "info": "\"Students are not allowed to chew gum in school, but teachers do it with impunity.\"",
        "id": 216
    },
    {
        "answer": "not injurious to physical or mental health; lacking intent or capacity to injure",
        "question": "innocuous",
        "info": "\"Athletes are always looking for fuel, no matter how innocuous the material might appear.\"",
        "id": 217
    },
    {
        "answer": "extraordinary in some bad way",
        "question": "egregious",
        "info": "\"an egregious mistake\"",
        "id": 218
    },
    {
        "answer": "to be celebrated",
        "question": "resound",
        "info": "\"news that resounded through the nation\"",
        "id": 219
    },
    {
        "answer": "having the power to perpetuate itself or oneself for an indefinite length of time",
        "question": "self-perpetuating",
        "id": 220
    },
    {
        "answer": "hurtful, harmful; deadly, fatal",
        "question": "pernicious",
        "info": "\"pernicious teachings\"",
        "id": 221
    },
    {
        "answer": "offensively self-assertive",
        "question": "bumptious",
        "id": 222
    },
    {
        "answer": "the reddish glow on mountaintops just before sunrise and just after sunset",
        "question": "alpenglow",
        "id": 223
    },
    {
        "answer": "to bask in the sun",
        "question": "apricate",
        "id": 224
    },
    {
        "answer": "to lie in or be exposed to a pleasant warmth; to enjoy a pleasant situation",
        "question": "bask",
        "id": 225
    },
    {
        "answer": "to brighten with golden light",
        "question": "engild",
        "id": 226
    },
    {
        "answer": "an extraordinary thing, person, or event",
        "question": "lollapalooza",
        "id": 227
    },
    {
        "answer": "daily; usual",
        "question": "quotidian",
        "id": 228
    },
    {
        "answer": "a great fuss about something insignificant; an excessive amount of decoration",
        "question": "foofaraw",
        "id": 229
    },
    {
        "answer": "to confuse or upset",
        "question": "discombobulate",
        "id": 230
    },
    {
        "answer": "showing great joy",
        "question": "jubilant",
        "id": 231
    },
    {
        "answer": "endowed with or characterized by hearty, joyous humor or a spirit of good fellowship",
        "question": "jovial",
        "id": 232
    },
    {
        "answer": "an advocate",
        "question": "proponent",
        "id": 233
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a place) sunny; (of a person's skin) having an attractive tanned color",
        "question": "sun-kissed",
        "info": "\"a sun-kissed beach\"",
        "id": 234
    },
    {
        "answer": "to draw out or lengthen",
        "question": "protract",
        "info": "\"Language development is very protracted according to the late maturation of the posterior temporal lobe. It takes a very long time to develop language.\"",
        "id": 235
    },
    {
        "answer": "so foolish, unreasonable, or out of place as to be amusing",
        "question": "ludicrous",
        "info": "\"Elon Musk has a penchant for silly names, hence Ludicrous Mode and now Bioweapon Defense Mode as the name for the air purification system on the Tesla\u2019s Models S and X\"",
        "id": 236
    },
    {
        "answer": "requiring or using great effort or exertion",
        "question": "strenuous",
        "info": "\"The government made strenuous efforts to upgrade the quality of the teaching profession.\"",
        "id": 237
    },
    {
        "answer": "unnecessary, especially through being more than enough",
        "question": "superfluous",
        "info": "\"The purchaser should avoid asking for superfluous information.\"",
        "id": 238
    },
    {
        "answer": "speak or write about someone or something with great enthusiasm and delight",
        "question": "rhapsodize",
        "info": "\"When former English majors rhapsodize about sentence diagramming, most people react as they would to expressions of nostalgia about algebra.\"",
        "id": 239
    },
    {
        "answer": "a figure of speech by which a part is put for the whole (as fifty sail for fifty ships), the whole for a part (as society for high society), the species for the genus (as cutthroat for assassin), the genus for the species (as a creature for a man), or the name of the material for the thing made (as boards for stage)",
        "question": "synecdoche",
        "id": 240
    },
    {
        "answer": "to prepare or make by combining ingredients, especially in cookery",
        "question": "concoct",
        "info": "\"Her brain cannot concoct the kind of healing she so desperately seeks.\"",
        "id": 241
    },
    {
        "answer": "to criticize (someone) severely",
        "question": "excoriate",
        "info": "\"\u201cThe practical spirit and the literary or scholastic spirit are both good, but they are incompatible,\u201d wrote Eliot in an 1869 piece in The Atlantic dubbed \u201cThe New Education.\u201d \u201cIf commingled, they are spoiled.\u201d\"",
        "id": 242
    },
    {
        "answer": "talk long-windedly without making very much sense",
        "question": "blather",
        "info": "\"She began blathering on about spirituality and life after death\"",
        "id": 243
    },
    {
        "answer": "the state of being extremely dirty and unpleasant, especially as a result of poverty or neglect",
        "question": "squalor",
        "info": "\"Why must you banish your old buddies to walk amongst the Unfriended, who must live in icy squalor like Divergent\u2019s Factionless or the White Walkers from Game of Thrones?\"",
        "id": 244
    },
    {
        "answer": "having or showing knowledge of events before they take place.",
        "question": "prescient",
        "info": "\"Scholze\u2019s work has a prescient quality, Weinstein said. \u201cHe can see the developments before they even begin.\u201d\"",
        "id": 245
    },
    {
        "answer": "a related or derived subject, problem, etc.; outgrowth; consequence; implication",
        "question": "ramification",
        "info": "\"Scholze\u2019s key innovation\u2014a class of fractal structures he calls perfectoid spaces\u2014is only a few years old, but it already has far-reaching ramifications in the field of arithmetic geometry, where number theory and geometry come together.\"",
        "id": 246
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of an animal) make a hole or tunnel, typically for use as a dwelling; make a thorough inquiry; investigate",
        "question": "burrow",
        "info": "\"As Scholze burrowed into the proof, he became captivated by the mathematical objects involved\u2014structures called modular forms and elliptic curves that mysteriously unify disparate areas of number theory, algebra, geometry and analysis.\"",
        "id": 247
    },
    {
        "answer": "raise objections or show reluctance",
        "question": "demur",
        "info": "\"Yet he is not at all inclined to romanticize this passion. Asked if he felt he was meant to be a mathematician, he demurred. \u201cThat sounds too philosophical,\u201d he said.\"",
        "id": 247
    },
    {
        "answer": "the language or dialect spoken by the ordinary people of a country or region",
        "question": "vernacular",
        "info": "\"Howl features Ginsberg\u2019s characteristic use of gritty vernacular and long lines, explicit sexuality, along with descriptions of abject people and places, and the stupor and ecstasy of drugs. \"",
        "id": 247
    },
    {
        "answer": "having plenty of money",
        "question": "well heeled",
        "info": "\"AWS was first to market with a modern cloud infrastructure service when it launched Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud in August, 2006. Surprisingly, it took several years before a competitor responded. As such, they control a vast amount of market share, at least for now. Rest assured, some very well-heeled competitors like Microsoft, Google, IBM and others are gunning for them.\"",
        "id": 248
    },
    {
        "answer": "the patterns of rhythm and sound used in poetry",
        "question": "prosody",
        "info": "\"The translator is not obliged to reproduce the prosody of the original.\"",
        "id": 249
    },
    {
        "answer": "rhythm of sound as it's spoken",
        "question": "cadence",
        "info": "\"\"In this audience, I see what's possible,\" he said, his voice adopting the cadence of a minister.\"",
        "id": 250
    },
    {
        "answer": "talk at length, especially in an inflated or empty way",
        "question": "bloviate",
        "info": "\"\"",
        "id": 251
    },
    {
        "answer": "a number of oxen, sheep, or swine driven in a group; herd; flock",
        "question": "drove",
        "info": "\"If Amazon Web Services\u2019 recent acquisition of Cloud9 is any indication, developers are flocking in droves toward cloud-based integrated development environments (IDEs).\"",
        "id": 252
    },
    {
        "answer": "isolate (one system, process, department, etc.) from others",
        "question": "silo",
        "info": "\"In short, there\u2019s never been more emphasis on the collaborative deployment of code. However, development workspaces and runtimes \u2014 which facilitate the actual editing, building, debugging and analyzing before code is committed to version control and sent to continuous integration \u2014 have remained siloed on localhost or VMs, caught in the IT/developer divide.\"",
        "id": 253
    },
    {
        "answer": "to avoid; to shun, to shy away from",
        "question": "eschew",
        "info": "\"While Amazon intends to offer its own cloud development environments through Cloud9, software giants like Google, Microsoft, Red Hat, SAP and Samsung eschew the rigidity of a closed system by opting for open-source projects like Eclipse Che and Eclipse Orion.\"",
        "id": 254
    },
    {
        "answer": "to produce, cause, or give rise to",
        "question": "engender",
        "info": "\"Curse words are different from the rest of language, as evidenced by how they seem to be exempt from regular rules of grammar and instead can engender their own.\"",
        "id": 255
    },
    {
        "answer": "describe or portray (something) precisely",
        "question": "delineate",
        "info": "\"Studies from people with different types of aphasia have delineated different brain regions that regulate different aspects of communication.\"",
        "id": 256
    },
    {
        "answer": "speak about (someone) in a spitefully critical manner",
        "question": "malign",
        "info": "\"People are more likely to discriminate against a group of people when they hear that group maligned, and members of the maligned group can be adversely affected as well.\"",
        "id": 257
    },
    {
        "answer": "to misunderstand the meaning of; take in a wrong sense; misinterpret",
        "question": "misconstrue",
        "info": "\"It\u2019s true people who have depression and anxiety can misconstrue, misquote and exaggerate.\"",
        "id": 258
    },
    {
        "answer": "remove (a need or difficulty)",
        "question": "obviate",
        "info": "\"Honestly, though, nobody else has four Thunderbolt 3 ports on a laptop yet, all of them allowing you to charge the laptop and obviating the MagSafe power plug.\"",
        "id": 259
    },
    {
        "answer": "relating to or denoting reasoning or knowledge which proceeds from theoretical deduction rather than from observation or experience",
        "question": "a priori",
        "info": "\"There is nothing that can be considered, a priori, to be part of the story, to be essential or inessential to the story.\"",
        "id": 260
    },
    {
        "answer": "be a sign or warning of (an imminent event, typically an unwelcome one)",
        "question": "presage",
        "info": "\"The heavy clouds above the moorland presaged snow.\"",
        "id": 261
    },
    {
        "answer": "a sudden and ignominious failure; a fiasco",
        "question": "debacle",
        "info": "\"Data feeds the weak AI we have now, and it produces spectacular results. But eventually, humanity must intervene, as evidenced by Microsoft's Twitter experiment or Facebook's censorship debacles.\"",
        "id": 262
    },
    {
        "answer": "in the style or manner of",
        "question": "\u00e0 la",
        "info": "\"If done correctly, packaging does one of two things: It disappears smoothly into the background of our consciousness because it is so seamless, beautiful and convenient; or it adds a dimension of delight and wonder to the unboxing process (\u00e0 la Apple).\"",
        "id": 263
    },
    {
        "answer": "an ancestral line; line of descent; lineage; ancestry",
        "question": "pedigree",
        "info": "\"Programmatic targeting is facing a similar issue, in an industry unsure how the coupling mechanism between man and machine should work. Sure, The New York Times has accurate data on its audience, but it also has a deep journalistic history and pedigree\u2014this context, of course, is lost on a programmatic robot. It takes a human touch to correctly leverage this pedigree.\"",
        "id": 264
    },
    {
        "answer": "The moment when a country or a society realizes that it needs to catch up with apparent technological and scientific developments made by some other country or countries by increasing its investment into education, innovative research and development, etc.",
        "question": "Sputnik moment",
        "info": "\"Sputnik moment is a reference to the Soviet Union\u2019s 1957 launch of the first Earth-orbiting artificial satellite Sputnik 1 which caught the USA unprepared. The event ignited the Space Race during the Cold War, and led to the USA successfully completing a human landing on the Moon in 1969.\"",
        "id": 265
    },
    {
        "answer": "The mark of the foot left on the earth; a track or footstep; a trace; a sign",
        "question": "vestige",
        "info": "\"The United States no longer controls the address book for the Internet. On Saturday, the US government handed the last vestiges of control to the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers, or ICANN, an independent organization whose members include myriad governments and corporations as well as individual Internet users.\"",
        "id": 266
    },
    {
        "answer": "an urgent need or demand",
        "question": "exigency",
        "info": "\"At a time when new media are proliferating, it is tempting to imagine that authors, thinking about how their writing will appear on devices such as electronic readers, tablet computers, or smartphones, consciously or unconsciously adapt their prose to the exigencies of publishing platforms.\"",
        "id": 267
    },
    {
        "answer": "imitate (someone or something), especially in an absurd or unthinking way",
        "question": "ape",
        "info": "\"Emily Gould, who has contributed to MIT Technology Review, is as responsible as anyone for the reigning style. In 2006, her blog, Emilymagazine, was noticed by the editors of Gawker, who hired her to write gossip about other young people working in media in New York. She was funny, acute, and oversharey; she became a microcelebrity and found her manner and coinages aped by other bloggers.\"",
        "id": 268
    },
    {
        "answer": "excessively sweet or sentimental",
        "question": "saccharine",
        "info": "\"It tends toward hype and hyperbole, mixed with the saccharine dead-on-arrival enthusiasm of American consumer service.\"",
        "id": 269
    },
    {
        "answer": "an act of attacking or plundering",
        "question": "depredation",
        "info": "\"A recent example of how authoring tools can suggest novel styles of writing can be found in Jennifer Egan\u2019s A Visit from the Goon Squad, which won the 2011 Pulitzer Prize for fiction. The novel, a collection of 13 interconnected short stories, describes the depredations of time (the goon squad of the title, because \u201ctime\u2019s a goon\u201d) upon a cast of characters who first meet in San Francisco\u2019s punk scene in the late 1970s.\"",
        "id": 270
    },
    {
        "answer": "prevent from happening; make impossible",
        "question": "preclude",
        "info": "\"When I\u2019m a woman I am mainly concerned with how my illness affects the emotional arc of some guy. When I\u2019m a man it\u2019s more likely that my illness manifests itself in me being really good at math. And yelling. If I am a male mentally ill person I do lots of yelling. As a woman my mental illness cannot be allowed to preclude my fuckability, so I do less yelling.\"",
        "id": 271
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a disease or condition) making someone very weak and infirm",
        "question": "debilitating",
        "info": "\"My illness is a curse, obviously, hence all the yelling, but in some ways it is also a blessing. After all, without it I would not be so good at art and/or game theory and/or ping-pong. It is the source of all my abilities even the ones that are normally the result of hard work and intellect rather than of a debilitating medical condition.\"",
        "id": 272
    },
    {
        "answer": "ordinary or basic",
        "question": "bog-standard",
        "info": "\"By the end of 108 minutes, will I be cured? That depends. Is this the sort of film that comes out in summer and is basically a bog-standard romantic comedy with the fun twist that one of the characters is ostensibly schizophrenic? Then sure! Love conquers all, even if all includes a chemical imbalance in someone\u2019s brain.\"",
        "id": 273
    },
    {
        "answer": "hinder or impede the movement or progress of",
        "question": "hamper",
        "info": "\"He wanted to write for television, but was hampered by self-doubt.\"",
        "id": 274
    },
    {
        "answer": "frown in an angry or bad-tempered way",
        "question": "scowl",
        "info": "\"Marooned on his sofa \u201clike a woozy sea lion,\u201d he spent weeks at a time scowling at the reality shows, talent competitions, and celebrity vehicles that were beginning to dominate Britain\u2019s programming.\"",
        "id": 275
    },
    {
        "answer": "lacking a plan, purpose, or enthusiasm",
        "question": "desultory",
        "info": "\"As a means of imposing order on his desultory existence, Brooker started a Web site, which he vowed to update every two weeks. \"",
        "id": 276
    },
    {
        "answer": "presented in vividly shocking or sensational terms",
        "question": "lurid",
        "info": "\"http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2016/11/28/the-speculative-dread-of-black-mirror\"",
        "id": 277
    },
    {
        "answer": "aware of what is going on; well informed",
        "question": "au courant",
        "info": "\"Ultimately, old or young, male or female, friendships take lots and lots of work to maintain. They don\u2019t just happen. Remembering people\u2019s birthdays. Checking how they are. Listening as well as talking, being interested and au courant in what they\u2019re up to.\"",
        "id": 278
    },
    {
        "answer": "(especially of a process or organization) just coming into existence and beginning to display signs of future potential",
        "question": "nascent",
        "info": "\"While Babbage possessed technical ingenuity, Aurora said, Lovelace propelled his invention into the nascent days of computing: \u201cShe was the first person to see the true potential.\u201d For this, Babbage called her \u201cLady Fairy.\u201d\"",
        "id": 279
    },
    {
        "answer": "incapable of being terminated; unending",
        "question": "interminable",
        "info": "\"This science constitutes the language through which alone we can adequately express the great facts of the natural world, and those unceasing changes of mutual relationship which, visibly or invisibly, consciously or unconsciously to our immediate physical perceptions, are interminably going on in the agencies of the creation we live amidst.\"",
        "id": 280
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a person's mouth) wide open in surprise or wonder",
        "question": "agape",
        "info": "\"On Zazzle, people can buy products emblazoned with an image of a stoic Trump raising the severed head of a bug-eyed Clinton, her mouth agape in silent protest\u2014an allusion to a sculpture by the Italian Renaissance artist Benvenuto Cellini.\"",
        "id": 281
    },
    {
        "answer": "very angry; enraged",
        "question": "incensed",
        "info": "\"In Ovid\u2019s story, the god Neptune sees Medusa, desires her, and decides that, because he is a god, he is entitled to her body (sound familiar?). He rapes her in Minerva\u2019s temple, and Minerva, incensed that her temple has been defiled, punishes the victim rather than the perpetrator (again, sound familiar?). \"",
        "id": 282
    },
    {
        "answer": "begin to grow or increase rapidly; flourish",
        "question": "burgeon",
        "info": "\"Medusa has since haunted Western imagination, materializing whenever male authority feels threatened by female agency. As the art historian Christine Corretti has explained, Cellini believed Medusa symbolized both the threat of women\u2019s burgeoning political power and a feminized Italy.\"",
        "id": 283
    },
    {
        "answer": "insulting, abusive, or highly critical language",
        "question": "invective",
        "info": "\"And as women rallied for the right to vote, various anti-suffrage postcards linked suffragettes to the monster. Concerns about gender and power continued into the 1940s when the writer Philip Wylie, in his invective Generation of Vipers, evoked Medusa (and her Gorgon sisters Stheno and Euryale) in order to urge readers to resist the women who had entered the work force after the first two world wars.\"",
        "id": 284
    },
    {
        "answer": "make (someone) feel annoyed or resentful",
        "question": "gall",
        "info": "\"Democracy is other people, and the ignorance of the many has long galled the few, especially the few who consider themselves intellectuals.\"",
        "id": 285
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of the weather) unpleasantly cold or wet",
        "question": "inclement",
        "info": "\"Rain fade can be mitigated by boosting the transmission power, by using larger dishes and hydrophobic coatings, or a fail-over protocol where the link drops down to a lower frequency that can better penetrate the inclement atmosphere when necessary.\"",
        "id": 286
    },
    {
        "answer": "having, inclined to have, or characterized by lascivious or lustful thoughts, desires, etc.",
        "question": "prurient",
        "info": "\"It is the curiosity and enthusiasm of youth rather than the prurience of age.\"",
        "id": 287
    },
    {
        "answer": "inclined to lustfulness; wanton; lewd",
        "question": "lascivious",
        "info": "\"a lascivious, girl-chasing old man\"",
        "id": 288
    },
    {
        "answer": "behaviour that is ridiculous but amusing",
        "question": "buffoonery",
        "info": "\"the film is full of wordplay and buffoonery\"",
        "id": 289
    },
    {
        "answer": "a comic dramatic work using buffoonery and horseplay and typically including crude characterization and ludicrously improbable situations",
        "question": "farce",
        "info": "\"In theatre, a farce is a comedy that aims at entertaining the audience through situations that are highly exaggerated, extravagant, and thus improbable.\"",
        "id": 290
    },
    {
        "answer": "relating to or resembling farce, especially because of absurd or ridiculous aspects",
        "question": "farcical",
        "info": "\"In lesser hands, he suggested, the premise would have turned farcical; Brooker\u2019s genius was to take \u201ca ridiculous idea and make it feel very rooted and real.\u201d\"",
        "id": 291
    },
    {
        "answer": "expand and contract with strong regular movements",
        "question": "pulsate",
        "info": "\"They are also the means by which Brooker persuades us to suspend our disbelief at the idea that the British government would give in to a kidnapper\u2019s demand, let alone the demand that is made of Michael Callow, the Prime Minister. Throughout the episode, the screen pulsates with news crawls and graphics, polling results, tweets.\"",
        "id": 292
    },
    {
        "answer": "grimly mocking or cynical",
        "question": "sardonic",
        "info": "\"We briefly see a video of the kidnapped Princess on YouTube; it has received 19,345,973 views and, in a sardonic touch, more likes (8,471) than dislikes (8,004).\"",
        "id": 293
    },
    {
        "answer": "crowd together; nestle closely",
        "question": "huddle",
        "info": "\"Brooker and Jones put on their headphones and huddled around the video monitors, which stood in front of an open fireplace.\"",
        "id": 294
    },
    {
        "answer": "stand, move, or sit in a lazy, drooping way",
        "question": "slouch",
        "info": "\"In the scene, Russell is slouched against a four-poster bed, pleading with two members of the video-game company to turn off the augmented-reality system.\"",
        "id": 295
    },
    {
        "answer": "complete lack of inhibition or restraint",
        "question": "abandon",
        "info": "\"Earlier, Brooker had suggested that Russell play the scene with even greater abandon than he had in previous takes; he wanted to insure that his frenzy was commensurate with the ghastly situation in which he found himself.\"",
        "id": 296
    },
    {
        "answer": "corresponding in size or degree; in proportion",
        "question": "commensurate",
        "info": "\"salary will be commensurate with age and experience\"",
        "id": 297
    },
    {
        "answer": "make a slight involuntary grimace or shrinking movement of the body out of pain or distress",
        "question": "wince",
        "info": "\"As Russell took another stab at it\u2014\u201cStop!\u201d he howled repeatedly, his voice at full stretch, while two impassive musclemen lugged him away\u2014Brooker flexed his eyebrows and winced. This seemed to signal approval.\"",
        "id": 298
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a person or process) diligent, thorough, and extremely attentive to details",
        "question": "scrupulous",
        "info": "\"As showrunner on \u201cBlack Mirror,\u201d Brooker is similarly scrupulous. The believability of each episode depends on maintaining the complex internal logic of its dystopic world, so he watches for the kinds of inconsistencies that can be unwittingly introduced during filming and editing.\"",
        "id": 299
    },
    {
        "answer": "excessively theatrical or dramatic in character or style",
        "question": "histrionic",
        "info": "\"\u201cIn Hollywood, if the hero receives an e-mail there\u2019ll be a giant animation of a fucking envelope spinning around,\u201d he said. \u201cWe try to avoid those kinds of histrionic computers.\u201d\"",
        "id": 300
    },
    {
        "answer": "crush (something, typically paper or cloth) so that it becomes creased and wrinkled",
        "question": "crumple",
        "info": "\"In the future world of the episode, deleting an e-mail simply requires making a fist in the air and opening your hand again, as though crumpling up a piece of paper and tossing it away.\"",
        "id": 301
    },
    {
        "answer": "In a novel, theatrical script, screenplay, sketch stories, and poetry, a vignette is a short impressionistic scene that focuses on one moment or character and gives a trenchant impression about that character, an idea, setting, and/or object. It's a short, descriptive passage that's more about evoking meaning through imagery than it is about plot.",
        "question": "vignette",
        "info": "\"In \u201cBe Right Back,\u201d the episode about the software for the bereaved, the female protagonist, whose husband has recently died in a car accident, receives an e-mail from an online bookseller with the subject line \u201cMartha, people in your position bought the following.\u201d When she opens it, the message shows an array of grief-counselling books, each accompanied by customer reviews. We glimpse the screen, and Martha\u2019s irritated response to it, for only a second. (In the future world of the episode, deleting an e-mail simply requires making a fist in the air and opening your hand again, as though crumpling up a piece of paper and tossing it away.) But the vignette stands for an accumulation of such intrusive moments\u2014the death of solitude by a thousand digital cuts.\"",
        "id": 302
    },
    {
        "answer": "the fact of knowing something in advance; foreknowledge",
        "question": "prescience",
        "info": "\"At the root of the show\u2019s creepy prescience lies Brooker\u2019s entrepreneurial grasp of what people desire, or might be made to desire. He frequently receives tweets and e-mails about real-world developments that echo details from the show.\"",
        "id": 303
    },
    {
        "answer": "dissatisfied, especially with people in authority or a system of control",
        "question": "disaffected",
        "info": "\"a military plot by disaffected elements in the army\"",
        "id": 304
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a bad or harmful act) intentional; deliberate",
        "question": "wilful",
        "info": "\"wilful acts of damage\"",
        "id": 305
    },
    {
        "answer": "difficult to control or predict because of wilful or perverse behaviour",
        "question": "wayward",
        "info": "\"For all its imaginative range, Brooker\u2019s work regularly returns to a particular character type: the wayward, disaffected young man who has more rage than he knows what to do with.\"",
        "id": 306
    },
    {
        "answer": "affected by bitterness, resentment, or cynicism",
        "question": "jaundiced",
        "info": "\"Nathan Barley spends much of his time trying to win the approval of a jaundiced hack named Dan Ashcroft, who has won minor celebrity for his articles deriding \u201cthe idiots\u201d who make up his milieu, those \u201cself-regarding consumer slaves\u201d who \u201cbabble into handheld twit machines.\u201d\"",
        "id": 307
    },
    {
        "answer": "express contempt for; ridicule",
        "question": "deride",
        "info": "\"Nathan Barley spends much of his time trying to win the approval of a jaundiced hack named Dan Ashcroft, who has won minor celebrity for his articles deriding \u201cthe idiots\u201d who make up his milieu, those \u201cself-regarding consumer slaves\u201d who \u201cbabble into handheld twit machines.\u201d\"",
        "id": 308
    },
    {
        "answer": "a person's social environment",
        "question": "milieu",
        "info": "\"Nathan Barley spends much of his time trying to win the approval of a jaundiced hack named Dan Ashcroft, who has won minor celebrity for his articles deriding \u201cthe idiots\u201d who make up his milieu, those \u201cself-regarding consumer slaves\u201d who \u201cbabble into handheld twit machines.\u201d\"",
        "id": 309
    },
    {
        "answer": "establish or settle (someone) in a comfortable, safe place",
        "question": "ensconce",
        "info": "\"In 2000, Brooker began working on the satirical news program \u201cThe 11 O\u2019Clock Show\u201d and writing his TV column for the Guardian. A few years later, the column grew into a weekly review program, \u201cScreenwipe,\u201d in which Brooker, ensconced in the living room of his South London flat, wryly taxonomized TV conventions (\u201cTV presenters are basically imaginary friends, and they come in four main types \u201d) and delivered baroquely vituperative monologues straight into the camera.\"",
        "id": 310
    },
    {
        "answer": "bitter and abusive",
        "question": "vituperative",
        "info": "\"In 2000, Brooker began working on the satirical news program \u201cThe 11 O\u2019Clock Show\u201d and writing his TV column for the Guardian. A few years later, the column grew into a weekly review program, \u201cScreenwipe,\u201d in which Brooker, ensconced in the living room of his South London flat, wryly taxonomized TV conventions (\u201cTV presenters are basically imaginary friends, and they come in four main types \u201d) and delivered baroquely vituperative monologues straight into the camera.\"",
        "id": 311
    },
    {
        "answer": "The first decade of a century, such as 1900 to 1909 or 2000 to 2009, whose digit in the tens place is zero. The oughts, the noughties.",
        "question": "aughts",
        "info": "\"It is not always easy to distinguish between the crotchety couch pundit and Brooker himself. Shane Allen, a producer on \u201cThe 11 O\u2019Clock Show,\u201d told me about a New Year\u2019s Eve party in the early aughts at which Brooker, having spent most of the night sitting quietly by himself, rose from his chair, put on the song \u201cI Hate People,\u201d by the hardcore punk group the Anti-Nowhere League (chorus: \u201cI hate people / I hate the human race / I hate people / I hate your ugly face\u201d), proceeded to \u201cwave his arse at everybody in the room, singing the song word for word, and then just sat down as though nothing had happened.\u201d\"",
        "id": 312
    },
    {
        "answer": "cause (someone) to feel very embarrassed or ashamed",
        "question": "mortify",
        "info": "\"In 2008, Brooker received a spoof news article from one of his admirers about Kerry Katona, a member of the British pop group Atomic Kitten. Katona, who had a history of drug addiction, had recently appeared on the daytime talk show \u201cThis Morning\u201d to promote a new reality series. She was clearly intoxicated, and her speech veered in and out of intelligibility. The article described Katona as a \u201cmentally hilarious ex-girl band jizz puppet\u201d and a \u201cpram-faced shit-muncher.\u201d Brooker was mortified. \u201cI couldn\u2019t work out which was worse,\u201d he wrote in the Guardian. \u201cThe fact that they\u2019d written this in the first place or the assumption that I, specifically, would find it funny.\u201d\"",
        "id": 313
    },
    {
        "answer": "indecent; salacious",
        "question": "scabrous",
        "info": "\"\u201cBlack Mirror\u201d is as scabrous as anything Brooker has done, but it is also clearly the work of a person who has thought through the risks and limitations of default-mode misanthropy.\"",
        "id": 314
    },
    {
        "answer": "a dislike of humankind",
        "question": "misanthropy",
        "info": "\"\u201cBlack Mirror\u201d is as scabrous as anything Brooker has done, but it is also clearly the work of a person who has thought through the risks and limitations of default-mode misanthropy.\"",
        "id": 315
    },
    {
        "answer": "referring to sexual matters in an amusingly rude or irreverent way",
        "question": "ribald",
        "info": "\"In \u201cThe Waldo Moment,\u201d the episode about a blue cartoon bear who successfully stands for Parliament, the disaffected public can\u2019t get enough of Waldo\u2019s ribald anti-politics.\"",
        "id": 316
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a person or their manner) childishly sulky or bad-tempered",
        "question": "petulant",
        "info": "\"he was moody and petulant\"",
        "id": 317
    },
    {
        "answer": "complaining in a rather petulant or whining manner",
        "question": "querulous",
        "info": "\"The bill arrived, and Brooker insisted on paying. The pin pad blipped obediently as he entered his number, then let out a low, querulous screech.\"",
        "id": 318
    },
    {
        "answer": "abrupt in manner; blunt; rough",
        "question": "brusque",
        "info": "\"A brusque welcome greeted his unexpected return.\"",
        "id": 319
    },
    {
        "answer": "arrogant and domineering",
        "question": "imperious",
        "info": "\"his imperious demands\"",
        "id": 320
    },
    {
        "answer": "insisting on immediate attention or obedience, especially in a brusquely imperious way",
        "question": "peremptory",
        "info": "\"Truth \u201cperemptorily claims to be acknowledged and precludes debate,\u201d Hannah Arendt pointed out in this magazine, in 1967, \u201cand debate constitutes the very essence of political life.\u201d\"",
        "id": 321
    },
    {
        "answer": "tending to stir up conflict",
        "question": "incendiary",
        "info": "\"First, one could deny that truth was a suitable standard for measuring political judgment. This sounds extreme, but it\u2019s a fairly common move in political philosophy. After all, in debates over contentious issues, such as when human life begins or whether human activity is warming the planet, appeals to the truth tend to be incendiary.\"",
        "id": 322
    },
    {
        "answer": "causing or likely to cause an argument; controversial",
        "question": "contentious",
        "info": "\"First, one could deny that truth was a suitable standard for measuring political judgment. This sounds extreme, but it\u2019s a fairly common move in political philosophy. After all, in debates over contentious issues, such as when human life begins or whether human activity is warming the planet, appeals to the truth tend to be incendiary.\"",
        "id": 323
    },
    {
        "answer": "a person who fights with the fists; a boxer, usually a professional",
        "question": "pugilist",
        "info": "\"Brennan has a bright, pugilistic style, and he takes a sportsman\u2019s pleasure in upsetting pieties and demolishing weak logic.\"",
        "id": 324
    },
    {
        "answer": "give (someone) a noble rank or title",
        "question": "ennoble",
        "info": "\"Voting rights may happen to signify human dignity to us, he writes, but corpse-eating once signified respect for the dead among the Fore tribe of Papua New Guinea. To him, our faith in the ennobling power of political debate is no more well grounded than the supposition that college fraternities build character.\"",
        "id": 325
    },
    {
        "answer": "to strike with or as if with something flat or heavy : whack",
        "question": "thwack",
        "info": "\"How would an epistocracy actually work? Brennan is reluctant to get specific, which is understandable. It was the details of utopia that gave Plato so much trouble, and by not going into them Brennan avoids stepping on the rake that thwacked Plato between the eyes.\"",
        "id": 326
    },
    {
        "answer": "a supernatural being in folklore and children's stories, typically portrayed as small and human-like in form, with pointed ears and a pointed hat",
        "question": "pixie",
        "info": "\"Without more details, it\u2019s difficult to assess Brennan\u2019s proposal. Suppose I claim that pixies always make selfless, enlightened political decisions and that therefore we should entrust our government to pixies.\"",
        "id": 327
    },
    {
        "answer": "having or showing keen mental discernment and good judgement; wise or shrewd",
        "question": "sagacious",
        "info": "\"If I can\u2019t really say how we\u2019ll identify the pixies or harness their sagacity, and if I also disclose evidence that pixies may be just as error-prone as hobbits and hooligans, you\u2019d be justified in having doubts.\"",
        "id": 328
    },
    {
        "answer": "a defensive wall",
        "question": "bulwark",
        "info": "\"Bear in mind that, during the current Presidential race, it looks as though the votes of blacks and women will serve as a bulwark against the most reckless demagogue in living memory, whom white men with a college degree have been favoring by a margin of forty-seven per cent to thirty-five per cent.\"",
        "id": 329
    },
    {
        "answer": "(of a tax or other charge) extremely high",
        "question": "punitive",
        "info": "\"The political scientist Scott Althaus has calculated that a voter with more knowledge of politics will, on balance, be less eager to go to war, less punitive about crime, more tolerant on social issues, less accepting of government control of the economy, and more willing to accept taxes in order to reduce the federal deficit.\"",
        "id": 330
    },
    {
        "answer": "the holder of an office or post",
        "question": "incumbent",
        "info": "\"Brennan doubts that voters understand party stereotypes well enough to do even this, but surely a shortcut needn\u2019t be perfect to be helpful. Voters may also rely on the simple heuristic of throwing out incumbents who have made them unhappy, a technique that in political science goes by the polite name of \u201cretrospective voting.\u201d\"",
        "id": 331
    },
    {
        "answer": "annoyance or distress at having failed or been humiliated",
        "question": "chagrin",
        "info": "\"But even if retrospective voting is sloppy, and works to the chagrin of the occasional pharaoh, that doesn\u2019t necessarily make it valueless. It might, for instance, tend to improve elected officials\u2019 policy decisions.\"",
        "id": 332
    },
    {
        "answer": "the animals of a particular region, habitat, or geological period",
        "question": "fauna",
        "info": "\"Pretty much every kind of flora and fauna in Australia can kill you. Seriously, take it from someone who was born there: Every crazy story you hear about Australian wildlife probably has some basis in reality.\"",
        "id": 333
    },
    {
        "id": 334,
        "question": "culpable",
        "info": "\"I submit that the unifying core, the essence of jerkitude in the moral sense, is this: the jerk culpably fails to appreciate the perspectives of others around him, treating them as tools to be manipulated or idiots to be dealt with rather than as moral and epistemic peers.\"",
        "answer": "meriting condemnation or blame especially as wrong or harmful"
    },
    {
        "id": 335,
        "question": "modicum",
        "info": "\"All normal jerks distribute their jerkishness mostly down the social hierarchy, and to anonymous strangers. Waitresses, students, clerks, strangers on the road \u2013 these are the unfortunates who bear the brunt of it. With a modicum of self-control, the jerk, though he implicitly or explicitly regards himself as more important than most of the people around him, recognises that the perspectives of those above him in the hierarchy also deserve some consideration.\"",
        "answer": "a small quantity of a particular thing, especially something desirable or valuable"
    },
    {
        "id": 336,
        "question": "vestigial",
        "info": "\"Perhaps the jerk retains a vestigial kind of concern specifically for those whom it would benefit him, directly or indirectly, to win over.\"",
        "answer": "forming a very small remnant of something that was once greater or more noticeable"
    },
    {
        "id": 337,
        "question": "malfeasance",
        "info": "\"Russia has conducted some of its malfeasance through digital means\u2014the U.S. intelligence community publicly accused Russia\u2019s intelligence services of hacking the Democratic National Committee and Hillary Clinton\u2019s campaign chairman, John Podesta.\"",
        "answer": "Wrongdoing"
    },
    {
        "id": 338,
        "question": "linchpin",
        "info": "\"For decades after the CIA was created in 1947, the agency focused on providing policymakers with the best possible information about enemy plans, intentions and motivations, and human intelligence was the linchpin of that.\"",
        "answer": "a central cohesive source of stability and security; a person or thing that is critical to a system or organisation"
    },
    {
        "id": 339,
        "question": "paraphernalia",
        "info": "\"The Washington Post reported last year that staff members at the U.S. Embassy in Moscow have been under increasingly heavy surveillance, subject to slashed tires on their cars, routine police stops and general intimidation. In 2013, the Russians arrested an American diplomat they suspected of spying, posted embarrassing photos of bizarre and wacky items they claimed were his spy paraphernalia\u2014including unconvincing wigs and glasses\u2014and then kicked him out of the country.\"",
        "answer": "miscellaneous articles, especially the equipment needed for a particular activity"
    },
    {
        "id": 340,
        "question": "broach",
        "info": "\"But what should we do if we really do want to de-friend someone\u2014without all the negative side effects? \u201cThe best solution,\u201d Rosen says, \u201cis for the two of you to mutually decide to delete each other on social media.\u201d While the subject can be uncomfortable to broach, he suggests that having a discussion about the decision can be better for your mental health and the quality of your now-distant relationship.\"",
        "answer": "raise (a difficult subject) for discussion"
    },
    {
        "id": 341,
        "question": "comportment",
        "info": "\"Scooby-Doo is not a dog. Granted, he does have the comportment and vocal characteristic of a canine, but this is, in fact, the tragic consequence of a botched elective surgery that Scooby underwent at the hands of his friend Shaggy, who was briefly enrolled in a plastic-surgery program at a medical school that he no longer attends.\"",
        "answer": "personal bearing or conduct; demeanor; behavior."
    }
]